<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Assignment10</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="home_title">Home</string>
    <string name="about_us_title">About Us</string>
    <string name="admissions_title">Admissions</string>
    <string name="academics_title">Academics</string>
    <string name="departments_title">Departments</string>
    <string name="placements_title">Placements</string>
    <string name="nirf_title">NIRF</string>

    <string name="home_description">Welcome to Bonam Venkata Chalamayya Engineering College.</string>
    <string name="about_us_description"><![CDATA[Our vision is to become a leading technical institute of
        academic excellence by imparting high patterns of discipline through innovative
        programmes of global standards making our students technologically superior and
        ethically strong to serve the nation.<br/><br/>
        And our mission is to create an environment that shall foster the growth of intellectually
        capable,innovative professionals who can contribute to the to the growth of technology in
        partnership with industry and develop and harness it for the welfare of the nation and
        mankind.]]></string>

    <string name="admissions_desc" formatted="true" translatable="true">
        <![CDATA[
        <p><h2>Allotments of Seats-B.Tech</h2></p>
            <p>The seats to be allotted in our institutions under the rules for Admissions are classified as :</p>
            <p>The Category A seats shall be 70% of sanctioned intake of seats in which course which shall be filled with eligible candidates on the basis of rank obtained at EAMCET /JEE.</p>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="academics_des">
        A library is the heart of an academic institution. Our institution encourages all students and
        staff members to make the best use of the library that has been carefully built up since the
        inception of the college. The library is housed in a spacious area of 1200 sq.m., The library
        is fully air-conditioned with internet connection for accessing e-journals and other sites of
        interest. The library is fully automated with Bees Campus Soft library management software system.
        Presently there are more than 36,000 books and 6500 reference volumes stacked for the benefit of
        staff and students. There is an established media resource centre. Our library follows the open
        access system and is encouraging students to browse in the stack area. The library subscribes
        more than 100 printed journals (both subject and general) and subscribed 3500 e-journals under
        AICTE mandatory (IEEE, Elsevier (Sciencedirect), Wiley, ASCE, Springer, J-Gate, Mc Graw-Hill and
        ASTM). We are also a member of Delnet.
    </string>
    <string name="departments_desc">
        <![CDATA[<p><h2>Departments</h2></p><p>&#8226;CSE<br />&#8226;ME<br />&#8226;EEE<br />&#8226;ECE<br />&#8226;CE</p>]]>
    </string>

    <string name="nirf_desc">

    </string>

    <string name="placement_desc">
        “Education for Excellence….Our MOTTO 100% Placements for all eligible candidates”

        BVC Institutions specially focus on Training and Placement for having a secured future .
        In this aspect full time faculty to teach aptitude and Soft skills are being engaged
        along with regular curriculum.BVC is specially recognized by AICTE for training students
        in competitive examinations like GATE ,GRE,and TOEFL. Our regular recruiters are WIPRO ,
        SINGULARITY , SYNTEL, TREWPORT,HCL tech,BAYDATACOM,SRIRAM GROUP,ASHoK LEYLAND etc..
    </string>
</resources>
